The past year and a half at Tessl has been super transformative for me.
I've had the opportunity to take on so much more than I was doing before.
I've been trusted with so much.
And I've been able to work with just super smart people
in a really interesting and challenging space.
What first attracted me to Tessl was definitely the team.
They're a wonderful
mix of super intelligent people and really low ego and really kind.
And the opportunity
to work with Guy so closely, it's just something you can't really say
no to Every six months we have these amazing off-sites.
We've been to Mallorca, we've been to Barcelona.
We have something really exciting planned for July.
We do a ton of working sessions, hackathons, demos,
really digging into problem
spaces that we don't get the chance to in the day to day at the office.
And then, of course, we tie that around with plenty of opportunity to socialise.
Plenty of great food and drink.
I think we've built a really great office experience, at Tessl.
So we've built out an amazing
10,000 square foot space in the middle of King's Cross.
We host a ton of AI communities here, and, we have the team onsite
three days a week, which means we can have a ton of lunches,
social celebrations, presentations together.
That means we get that face to face collaboration.
The culture we have at Tessl is unique
because we are led by an incredible founder who has done this before
and because we are a group of people who come from
a range of different backgrounds, who have all done incredible things.
And we're now aligned on this journey.
I am a people person through and through.
It's what excites me and energises me.
And I get to be surrounded by the most intelligent, interesting people
and probably the most interesting space you could be in right now in the world.
I don't suffer from the Sunday scaries, which is a really unique thing.
I always know that something interesting is going to happen in my week,
and it's usually not what I expect to happen.
I think I've been so trusted to take on more than I ever thought I could.
And I can only imagine that that's just going to grow and grow.
And I'm really grateful for that opportunity.
I truly can't wrap my head around what could come next,
but I know I'm in such safe hands and the right environment to just take on
whatever this wonderful journey brings.